<resources>
    <string name="app_name">HousingSocietyApp</string>


    <string name="homeActivity">Home</string>
    <string name="profileActivity">Profile</string>
    <string name="historyActivity">History</string>

    <string name="dialog"> SignOut Dialog</string>

    <string name="notice1">This is noticed that some notorious people or group " +
                    "of people are damaging and making scratches on the vehicles in the society. " +
                    "This is humble request to all the residents to keep their eye " +
                    "and ear open towards such nuisance creators.\n" +
                    "\n" +
                    "Kindly be vigilant and inform the security personels whenever" +
                    " you are on vacation or on long travel and your house is locked" +
                    " so that security personells can be more vigilant and careful.</string>

    <string name="notice2">The meeting shall sharp start at 10.30 am. If the quorum of the meeting" +
                    " is not present at that time, the meeting shall be adjourned for another half an hour from 10.30 am. The adjourne" +
                    "d meeting take place 11.00 am at the same date and venue. In the adjourned meeting no quorum is necessary.</string>
    <string name="notice3">"Dear Residents,\n" +
                    "\n" +
                    "Resident Welfare Association would like to inform you that " +
                    "a new scrap dealer, Mr. Mahesh Chand has been appointed in" +
                    " place of old scrap dealer Mr. Subhash.\n" +
                    "\n" +
                    "So from now (1st January 2015), RWA authorize Mr Mahesh as" +
                    " the new scrap dealer for Sanskriti Apartments. RWA have" +
                    " made a legal contract with him and fixed a fees of" +
                    " Rs. 6000/- per month (Rs. 72000 per annum) in comparison" +
                    " to the previous one which was Rs. 1000/- per month (Rs. 12000/- per annum)."</string>


    //FireBase Text

    <string name="google_status_fmt"> Edit Profile </string>
    <string name="firebase_status_fmt"> Edit Profile </string>
    <string name="auth_failed"> Authentication Failed </string>

    //Spinner Array
    <string-array name="bill_type">
        <item>Select Vehicle Type</item>
        <item>Flat Rent</item>
        <item>Electricity Bill</item>
        <item>Parking Rent</item>
        <item>Water Bill</item>
        <item>Maintenance Charge</item>
        <item>Security Charges</item>
    </string-array>

    // Database nodes name

    <string name="db_user"> user </string>
    <string name="db_user_settings"> user_settings </string>

    //FireBase Fields
    <string name="field_username"> username </string>
    <string name="field_dispalyName"> display_name </string>
    <string name="field_email"> email </string>
    <string name="field_mobileNo"> mobile_no </string>

</resources>
